[

    {
        "question": "Born in September",
        "answer": ["taft"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Arkansas",
        "answer": ["clinton"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in California",
        "answer": ["nixon"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Connecticut",
        "answer": ["bush_gw"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Georgia",
        "answer": ["carter"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Hawaii",
        "answer": ["obama"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Illinois",
        "answer": ["reagan"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Iowa",
        "answer": ["hoover"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Kentucky",
        "answer": ["lincoln"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Missouri",
        "answer": ["truman"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in Nebraaska",
        "answer": ["ford"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in New Hampshire",
        "answer": ["pierce"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Born in New Jersey",
        "answer": ["cleveland"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Held the office of govenor of Indiana Territory",
        "answer": ["harrison_wh"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Held the office of governor-general of the Philippines",
        "answer": ["taft"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Held the office of New York State Comptroller",
        "answer": ["fillmore"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Held the office of sherriff",
        "answer": ["cleveland"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Served as U.S. Secretary of Commerce",
        "answer": ["hoover"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Served as Director of Central Intelligence",
        "answer": ["bush_ghw"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Served as Collector of the Port of New York",
        "answer": ["arthur"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Served as Chief Justice of the U.S. Supreme Court",
        "answer": ["taft"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "Served as speaker of the U.S. House of Representatives",
        "answer": ["polk"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    }, 

        {
        "question": "Served as president pro tempore of the U.S. Senate",
        "answer": ["tyler"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    }, 

            {
        "question": "Native speaker of Dutch",
        "answer": ["vanburen"],
        "answerNumber": 1
    }

]